<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <title>THE ARCHIVES</title>
    <link href="https://augustenian.github.io/the-archives/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://augustenian.github.io/the-archives" />
    <updated>2025-03-20T20:10:45-05:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Erin</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://augustenian.github.io/the-archives</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Welcome!</title>
        <author>
            <name>Erin</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://augustenian.github.io/the-archives/a.html"/>
        <id>https://augustenian.github.io/the-archives/a.html</id>

        <updated>2025-03-20T18:55:23-05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Hello, world! I'm Erin, the author of every written thing on this website, and I'm here to extend a hand in welcome! Whether&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                
  <p>
    Hello, world!
<br>
<br>I'm Erin, the author of every written thing on this website, and I'm here to extend a hand in welcome! Whether you came across this site from Google, found me on Twitter/X, or some secret third option, I hope that you find something to your liking here (even if the only thing that you like is the site itself).
<br>
<br>More about me can be found under the About tab.
<br>
<br>But the purpose of this post isn't to introduce myself, it's to introduce this place - home of multiple and infinite projects that are dear to me.
<br>
<br>This page - the home page - will be where a blog of sorts resides. I'll be using it to notify everyone of updates, and occasionally churn out a piece about writing-related thoughts and inspirations.
<br>
<br>I'll try to restrain the amount of activism that I display here, but given my own identity and the stories that I choose to tell, that may not hold.
<br>
<br>The "What's Happening?" page lets you know what stage I am on any current projects that I'm juggling. Information includes a short description of each goal, along with a progress bar showing how far along I am. Everything else is fairly self-explanatory - a "Short Stories" page for easy access to my short stories; a "Novels" page for easy access to my novels; and a "Miscellaneous" page for any stories written in a non-traditional format, along with any articles or story collections.
<br>
<br>And…that's that. Feel free to give my Twitter a follow for more updates both personal and professional! See you all later!<br>
  </p>

  <p>
    
  </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
